<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lytedev</title>
    <link>https://lytedev.io/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on lytedev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>daniel@lytedev.io (Daniel Flanagan)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>daniel@lytedev.io (Daniel Flanagan)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 14:43:02 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://lytedev.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://lytedev.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 14:43:02 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>daniel@lytedev.io (Daniel Flanagan)</author>
      <guid>https://lytedev.io/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;div class=&#34;text-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://lytedev.io/img/daniel.jpg&#34; class=&#34;avatar&#34; alt=&#34;A photo of Daniel taken on his wedding day.&#34; title=&#34;Daniel&#34;&gt;
        &lt;figcaption style=&#34;visibility:hidden;height:0&#34;&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;introductions&#34;&gt;Introductions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Daniel Flanagan. Yes, I &lt;strong&gt;always&lt;/strong&gt; dress up like that. I was born in
Virginia (but my family didn&amp;rsquo;t stay long) and now live in Kansas City, Missouri.
My family lives here, too! I have 6 awesome little brothers. Yes, my parents had
seven boys and are fantastic. I love my family quite a lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer and an elder-in-training for the small church I&amp;rsquo;ve been
a part of since its conception in 2012 or so called Rising. I also run all the
tech and audio-visual systems there and I love it. My faith is the framework
around which I&amp;rsquo;ve built my life and it has never failed me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a big proponent of self-discipline, working from home, and working less than
40 hours per week. My favorite video games include &lt;em&gt;Super Smash Bros. Melee&lt;/em&gt;,
&lt;em&gt;Quake 3&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;World of Warcraft&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Counter Strike: Global Offensive&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Portal&lt;/em&gt;,
&lt;em&gt;Half-Life 2&lt;/em&gt;, and others. I listen to a lot of metal (&lt;em&gt;DragonForce&lt;/em&gt;!) and
electronic music. My favorite drink is &lt;em&gt;Red Bull Yellow Edition&lt;/em&gt; and I prefer
tea over coffee. I run Arch Linux on all my machines and have almost got my wife
to switch over to Ubuntu, though in fairness it&amp;rsquo;s mostly due to her MacBook
beginning to show its age. I have an odd obsession with mechanical keyboards
(thanks, reddit).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;text-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://lytedev.io/img/daniel-and-valerie.jpg&#34; class=&#34;avatar&#34; alt=&#34;Daniel and his wife in a forest.&#34; title=&#34;Daniel and Valerie&#34;&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;My wife and I. Yes. It&#39;s true. I only have the &lt;strong&gt;one&lt;/strong&gt; pose.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m married to Valerie, the most beautiful woman in the entire world. She&amp;rsquo;s
a trained and working Physical Therapist Assistant and somewhat of a fitness
and health nut, which has yet to rub off on me (darn!). We&amp;rsquo;ve been married since
late 2016 and we fall more in love every day. We currently live in a cozy little
apartment which she somehow manages to keep clean, organized, and
well-decorated, between working her two jobs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could talk about her for quite a long time, but this probably isn&amp;rsquo;t the place
to do that. We (sort of) run a blog at
&lt;a href=&#34;https://danielandvalerie.life&#34;&gt;danielandvalerie.life&lt;/a&gt; and we&amp;rsquo;ll hopefully get around
to putting her bio up on there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;history&#34;&gt;History&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I grew up not around the dining table, but around the keyboard or latest
Nintendo console; video games were bonding and family time. I discovered
programming through my dad (whom I refer to as &amp;ldquo;Daddy&amp;rdquo;) who showed me QBASIC
after I persisted in asking how video games were made. Within a few weeks I had
made a simple snake game and he bought me a book title &lt;em&gt;C# for the Absolute
Beginner&lt;/em&gt; and that was it. I was hooked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I moved from C# to the web quite naturally, as the things I wanted to make were
community-oriented and I loved the idea of users or friends not needing to
install anything to use what I made. I had a job washing cars after I dropped
out of high school (because college was expensive and time consuming and I could
already write code&amp;hellip; so I thought!) when a recruiter found some of my work and
landed me my first programming gig at a small web company in town that owned
some popular online services and made money via ads and was focused on M&amp;amp;A.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that company went down, I binge watched the office before I realized
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t just laze around forever. I called my recruiter and landed another
position at &lt;a href=&#34;https://emfluence.com&#34;&gt;emfluence&lt;/a&gt;, a digital marketing firm in downtown KC.
These guys were (and are!) fantastic and a part of me really misses the
environment. After a year or so of working there, I was let go as my boss sensed
a lack of drive or interest in what the company was doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a month or so of trying to figure out what to do, my financial advisor
contacted me about possibly making some web applications for him and I realized
I could totally freelance! &lt;a href=&#34;https://iqcalculators.com&#34;&gt;IQ Wealth Calculators&lt;/a&gt; was born and I was hired
to create the calculator(s) side of things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then, I&amp;rsquo;ve been picking up and hunting down any work I can, primarily here
in Kansas City. I have a big heart for Christian organizations and have
volunteered/donated my abilities wherever and whenever I can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To this day I dream of someday making video games for a living. It&amp;rsquo;s a shame the
game development industry is currently a bit overloaded.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://lytedev.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 14:43:02 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>daniel@lytedev.io (Daniel Flanagan)</author>
      <guid>https://lytedev.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;text-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;form action=&#34;https://formspree.io/daniel@lytedev.io&#34; method=&#34;POST&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;field&#34;&gt;
            &lt;label name=&#34;name&#34;&gt;Full Name&lt;/label&gt;
            &lt;input type=&#34;text&#34; name=&#34;name&#34; placeholder=&#34;Daniel Flanagan&#34; /&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;field&#34;&gt;
            &lt;label name=&#34;_replyto&#34;&gt;Email&lt;/label&gt;
            &lt;input type=&#34;email&#34; name=&#34;_replyto&#34; placeholder=&#34;you@gmail.com&#34; /&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;field&#34;&gt;
            &lt;label name=&#34;content&#34;&gt;Message&lt;/label&gt;
            &lt;textarea name=&#34;content&#34; rows=&#34;4&#34;&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;field&#34;&gt;
            &lt;input class=&#34;button primary&#34; type=&#34;submit&#34; value=&#34;Send&#34; /&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;input type=&#34;hidden&#34; name=&#34;_next&#34; value=&#34;/thanks&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;input type=&#34;hidden&#34; name=&#34;_subject&#34; value=&#34;Contact Form Submission - lytedev&#34; /&gt;
    &lt;/form&gt;
    &lt;small&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
            Email form not working for you? Just email me: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:daniel@lytedev.io&#34;&gt;daniel@lytedev.io&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://lytedev.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 14:43:02 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>daniel@lytedev.io (Daniel Flanagan)</author>
      <guid>https://lytedev.io/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Like millions of other websites, I use Google Analytics on lytedev.io. It records data about my visitors &amp;ndash; that&amp;rsquo;s you! It tracks what website you came form to get here, how long you stay, some information about the device you&amp;rsquo;re using to view lytedev.io, and some other information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do I do with this information? It helps me better understand the kind of people come to my site and what content they’re reading. This allows me to make better decisions about design and writing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Occasionally, I will compile aggregate statistics about the number of visitors this site receives and browsers being used. No personally identifying data is included in this type of reporting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of my activity falls within the bounds of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html&#34;&gt;Google Analytics Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&#34;lead text-center&#34;&gt;Done here? Head back to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://lytedev.io/&#34;&gt;home page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You!</title>
      <link>https://lytedev.io/thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 14:43:02 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>daniel@lytedev.io (Daniel Flanagan)</author>
      <guid>https://lytedev.io/thanks/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;thank-you-so-much-for-reaching-out&#34;&gt;Thank you so much for reaching out!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p class=&#34;text-center&#34;&gt;I usually reply within a day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&#34;text-center&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lytedev.io/&#34;&gt;Back to Home&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&#34;text-center&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lytedev.io/blog&#34;&gt;Or check out the blog!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>